That's the car,
go
Get out of the car
Get out.
hey
No no
Hold on...
hey
Two months later...
I see you going for two months.
Any question?
I have not seen any faces that come here so unhappily
I am alone ..
Nobody will help.
I thought that this would help me, too ..
But I do not feel like listening here
No son ..
There's no such thing.
God
Everyone is listening.
One time, son
Only once
confess your confession.
Certainly God sends someone for you...
Ranveer Singh in this operation... killing three people...
Explanations Have anything?
Sir, this is in accordance with military law.
No offensive damage
The three terrorists were civilians as civilians.
The Army's giants...
This is our box
Our path is stronger than your bullet
There is not a problem until then ..
What about the rest?
There is a violation of human rights. This is sir ..
A terrorist is being held hostage ..
coming out.
A man is going to kill himself to get out of the way
Where's the law?
It's not without methods, sir
Sir
Officer who went with him for this.
We suspend his activity
You decide yourself, sir.
Ranjit
- Sir
Captain Ranwher Pheap Singh
I also took my decision ..
You, with your reunion team
I will meet at the Training Grounds
And before I come...
You must be 25 miles [5 km] away.
Your time has just begun.
Start.
Ji Hind Sire ..
Sir ..
Your nurse saved your job from ninety nine
Is it fun?
It did not crad your phone ..
Take a look
We do not have the right to light our weapons
How can you do it?
They will say yes.
-  Hi Roni ..
Neha ..
Call four years later.
I'm not sure if you use the old one or not.
But if you can hear me...
Call me again.
989223583
Hey, Ronnie...
Forget that girl.
I know your situation.
Since then, there has been no connection since
Do not know what you want.
leave...
yesterday saved a disciplinary inquiry ..
Do you need a vacation today?
Yes, sir
Why should I go ..?
Personal work, sir ..
I think kids will understand you
Military does not have any personal task.
Not for four years left, sir.
Give me seven days, sir, for me.
Four years from these mountains
People who do not know how to deal with people
Let me handle it
Commando...
7 days for you...
On the first day of the first rays of the sun...... on the eighth day......
Unit...
Barracks...
Uniform...
And I...
You will be hoping...
Thank you, sir
Jai Hindi sir...
neha
Hi simmi
Neha please listen
What happened?
Ronnie's number was found...
What is Ronnie?
Ronnie...
Ronnie... Oh, no...
That's the one that did the school games
Yes, the slambol champion...
What about him?
- What about him? Come on.
see
Oh, is that it?
Yes, there is a guy in the basketball ball.
Let's phone.
Thank you.
Congratulations
Are you crazy?
Do you call him?
He does not even know if we know him -
Yah .. Hey, Ronnie
Who is this?
how nice you are...
proper bones
How did you make it?
fuck'd up
go go go
Can I know who I'm talking to?
Saved
Do not talk to us if we do not?
How do you say without the name?
What do you say ..?
How girls are talking about you How can I not speak to you?
What did the girls say about you...?
How do you know about me?
What is it you're about to do? - Hey Mr. Michael Jordan.
In your toy basketball basket, you are shown:
I'm not like girls ...
- Shut your mouth
So... Call... I did not...
This hello .. Call me back I did. My friend
Are u Happy now?
However... fortunate enough to talk to me right now
Or I did not meet a guy for more than two words with me.
Why did it happen...
Are you so ugly?
Ugly?
I'll see if I can see a photo...
I will  Of course ..?
Well, let's try and... turn around  What did you say?
what?
Listen
I'll let you stay on...
I know ..
I got a boyfriend
Sheeker his name
A well-developed man...
You will meet him...
- Hmm... Hmm... Hmm...
How are you doing Hmm...?
Hey, he came looking for you
I really like you.
Do you know...There are three reasons to love each other
The first mentality
Just a little madness
What do you think ..
The rest of you try to be more fun than her  He's gotta stay there like that.
I'm keenly drawn ..
Nice.
The second is emotional...
your heart ..
your friend stopped college coming
_ Why pay no money...
You paid for his fee...
She was given a college scholarship
The third thing is the physical nature
your smile...
Maybe you still have not seen it so beautiful...
That... you... you....... You have done your shame...
Fear and anger when you collected...
I like it a lot...
But I do not like you...
you... you must be his father ..?
Goodbye Sir
- Hello!
Hello
Nice to meet you
I went running over the headroom and went...
I did not see you...
I will go  a real car...
nice car...
I am... I'm Ronnie
Be careful of these people...
go to
Ask now.
I have three reasons for reluctant people
One... arrogance
two. More people. Readers who read the hell
Third...
You came after me...
I can not see those people...
Good things are yours...
Straight say what...
I would like to...
If I want to say something again....
Come to...  So soon...
So soon
come on!
my number?
Daddy does not want to jump, right?
Do not jump off like a crazy guy  Number
However...
Neha...
"God... you were worthy of suffering..."
"" The storm... you made a beach called "Me"... "
"O... the moon..."
"Without you..."
"The Right Way to Go"
"I do not see..."
"O... the moon..."
"Without you..."
"What to do..."
"I do not know..."
"After watching..."
"Do not know what is searching for..."
Even sleep has been forgotten...
"Sleep has been forgotten..."
Looking for fiction novels bundle stickers...
Even sleep has been forgotten...
"I can not even admit to sleep..."
"God... you were worthy of suffering..."
"" The storm... you made a beach called "Me"... "
"Without you..."
"The Right Way to Go"
"I do not see..."
I love you...
Found out...
Is this an upgraded version?
What happened?
It feels scary ..
At age seven ..
told a boy...
He set up my best friend and I kissed him
I know it's ridiculous.
It's been said to my mom...
It went away ..
Let's do this  Remember love and forget...
What did you say?
I mean ..
I do not want to say...  I need to feel...
like your mother...
Not at all .. but
You feel his love every day, do not you?
And I want to make my love everyday you...
What happens in life...
I'll be with you every day ..
Ronnie...
Hi
So .. how?
What are those spots?
It...
Are you ok?
Naha ..
- Hahh.
Uh...
How has it changed?
cut the hair
I am in the army now
Then
What happened to Slamball?
You like it very much
= The ball of bullion before four years...
So...
Are you married?
Uh... No, I'm... I'm happy.
Uh...
How about you?
- Kids like that?
There is a daughter ..
Oh...
great.
How beautiful a family?
Neha ..
After four years you remember me...
I said...
Why did not you mention the phone with the phone?
I need your help
The first day of school.
I did not want to go to him.
I like it somehow.
I went to school for about an hour.
The first day of schooling.
- Are you ready?
No ..
- Why? I'll find many friends ..
It's a lot to play.
- No.
- No, no. - Mmm
Know mom and mom when... the first day of school.
I was so scared.
But my mom got so much...
Come to school every day
Let's go.
What happened?
Sorrow?
Hmm ..
Want your favorite game?
and then go ..
Take this ..
and.
They kidnapped my daughter.
In a minute my whole life has changed.
I do not know what they want.
Help me find my daughter.
The poster, Ronnie.
pleace
I need your help
Please help me.
Help me find my daughter.
Sorry.
I need a car.
If you come to Goa, you will not forget two things.
The beer bar of every bend...
UMC car that ride on a road...
Huh?
But first the ID is for security.
Seven...
The whole world is safe for the entire country
Hey, chotu, take it soon.
Military officers have a great honor in my heart.
A lot ..
Here...
We kill each other on the streets at the same time...
among those you are like people...
Give their life for the country
Only once
once  you are so lazy...
The answer is on the basis of the answer  Huh?
Huh?
why you come to the gova?
personal use
- for personal use
I have come here for a personal purpose too.
Fifteen years ago.
Then I found this Russian cutlery.
Hey, Marion.
Marion ..
Both meals are made.
The children are looking after it.
Umsan ba... milk.
She did not say anything.
The noise has gone a lot.
Dope.
I felt the high volume of that silent guy ..
Life's too much out of life.
all my strengths were lost.
I just missed you.
You said it.
You always stand for me,
In life, whatever happens...
I'll be with you every day.
Today I need you Ronnie.
The time we were together was that life was the most beautiful thing
It will always be remembered.
Ria is my everything ..
I need your help
In the past two months nobody helped me.
I'm not selfish ..
I'm helpless with Ronnie.
Did you see my daughter, Raiya? - I did not see Ma'am
Did my daughter see Riya
- We do not know
I do not know. Really? I'm sorry to get this call.
What's the status of Shaker...?
Sheikren is too crazy.
= Shakeer to join Roya.
Where is my daughter? Where is Riah?
Uhah, police...?
The police...
-  Sir Sir Sir
What happened to my complaint?
Madam, we do not have any information.
One day I come home... that they say...
Madam has been investigating for two months.
No hints were found.
Your case was closed. Sign here.
- What nonsense?
Can I see them?
Ratod. Why was this file here?
This is inside.
It fixes the last bit ..
- All right, sir.
Hane .. Nihimah...
Come on.
Go in and you...
_ Are you in good health?
IP
- Yes, sir
Get Ma'am file.
- Come on, sir.
For months, look, madam.
No you did not sign it.
Sign it now. Madam, finish the case.
How will you do the case?
For two months it is investigated.
Nothing was found.
And you have nothing for us...
You did not give it.
Yes, sir
Hey.
Did you think that the library came?
ah?
Who is you?
A friend ..
Which national friend is madam?
A family friend ..
What kind of speech did you say to your friend.
This is not a story.
This also has to be there.
My boyfriend's missing. You're not doing anything.
Is it evidence that comes coming from the wind?
It's too expensive. This dog.
You stop the sound of the dog.
I want to come?
- Okay, sir
Ma'am...
We can not do anything purely.
But God will surely listen to your request.
Try it.
Go back.
She's forgotten where she is.
I told you to go back.
Stop him.
Or make it a side...
He'll be hit.
You shook my hand, too? B ..
Ronnie
Ma'am, if you stay here, the questions will increase.
But my friend is in. So...
I put my hand up to the police. She's madam.
But the situation is now under control.
Morning will release her tomorrow morning.
Please go...
- Are you sure?
Yes, inevitably.
Sir...
Sir, look here, sir.
Whoops, who the hell are you?
Sir, he's a soldier.
What? - Yes Sir
- Did not say before, because man ..?
Huh?
All right, we've bothered you so much
You were tortured
I find it encouraging.
This is not your borders
this is my area
No, no one rescued you, did you understand?
Hey, get up DIG sir is here.
DIG sir, come on, hurry up.
Dude, come on, DIG.
Ranver... Kapoor... who's...
Sir, this actor.
The one in the picture.
Sir A Ranwir Pratap Singh  There you go... bring it.
-
All right, sir.
Sir, DIG sir is talking.
DIG sir right now?
Get this one unclean.
Then you are
Ranweer Pratap Singh.
hmmm
Yes, sir
Do you know Ranwir?
My older brother was used to
I will be a doctor
I do not get up early in the morning
At night we have to go to emergency patients.
So I did not become a doctor.
But the case is.
This is a nightmare for people to find out.
It will not sleep.
This time.?
Do not you know how to respect the idol?
Know Sir
So, what did a police officer do with his hand?
He forgot his job.
I reminded you.
Who are you?
Is that God?
Hmm ..?
According to Section 475 of the Code of Criminal Procedure.
Do not you know that you can not arrest an army officer?
Are you an army?
This time out of office.
An official who is absent from duty is an identical to a civilian
That's what I know.
Give a second.
This is Ranjith ..
Did you go? Yes. Yes, I went.
This is your commando ..
He explains military rules.
Is there before you?
You call yourself
Your Colonel
Ji Hindi sir ..
- Jay Hind
Ronnie. Do you hear me?
- Yes, sir.
I'm happy about the DIG of Shergar who was a friend of my badge.
Or stay in the prison cell all night long.
Sir, sir. I can explain everything.
Ronnie, you explain it to yourself.
Tomorrow at seven o'clock.
I want you all an explanation.
Do you hear me?
- Yes, sir.
You are like his best guy.
Have you heard a story?
It's a garlic rot.
The whole stomach is caring ..
Is not it ..?
Go to go  Sir.
Ask this boy.
My brother used to say.
Once a soldier...
Always be a soldier...
After that ..
Be Responsible.
Because Sallier is going so early...
War on the border?
Tell us if you like...
I think the war is very violent  Not inside or inside of yours A girl's girlfriend?
oh, well ..
I understood ..
When a heart warms the heart...
Always ask the heart.
What the brain says... is normal
But the heart's... right.
Ria is my everything.
I need your help, Ronnie.
Can I help my daughter?
Whats in life...  I am with you every day ..
Turn Usman on Cars.
B...?
Turn the car around. Go to the hotel.
It looks like the heart, the brain is overwhelming (like)
Yes, what should I do? ..
Two months ago your school boy was kidnapped An abduction?
When?
- on Feb 7th
No, no such thing happened. You got a bad news.
Actually, a family friend told me.
A police investigation was made about it.
No, your child was never here.
See his photo...
Ria is his name
Ria SanGuccar ..
- Shark boy.
But this boy was not a schoolboy in our school = How to seize it from here?
There is no child in here.
Huh... Huh... Hah...
It's a great story, Shukla G .. Say, uh... and say ..
You are... you...
_ Give me a minute...
Yes ..?
Sir, sir, he was kidnapped two months ago.
With a car
So... what do you want me to do?
Do you know anything about it? Who are you?
Is it a cop?
- Family, sir
Watching...
- Yes sir  Send this guy ..
Private property can not come for the next time Sir, please, sir, sir
Wait a moment  Are not Meka still here?
Who is this?
Ronnie, it's all up to date yesterday. So much for...
I'm really sorry
- It's ok not to say.
Ria went to school.
Princeton says it did not look like
There was not a girl named Raiya.
- They usually say it like that.
appeal to this case.
But I can understand him
Anyone who does that  If you have a dispute, do you have a family, OK? Does Cole come in?
No... nothing happened.
What does Shaker say about this?
I see my condition and she is all hiding in her heart.
Can I talk to him?
Schaiker about us...
you do not know anything about yourself
Can you know who you were kidnapped?
- They were masked.
There will be some way.
Ronnie: I would like to ask for help.
Well.
Can I have Riauge more pictures for me?
No, I...
What did you mean...?
Somewhere.?
Social networks, phone, friends.
All friends are luxury.
Social networking is something far apart from me Shaker does not like this.
You're saying that your house, your daughter's one photo?
Sunny.
Sunny Shaker's brother.
Ronnie, you go quickly.
- Ronnie. Move it. - What's wrong?
Shaker's brother will know a big problem.
Please go
- so you can say
Please try to understand me, Ronnie.
Big problem here
Please go quickly.
Hey...
Baby. (Baby) I told you, Barbie Anybody there?
Who's at home?
Brother said to keep an eye on you  You know I'd like to be here.
I will make fun of you
They are making fun of.
Do you know?
Last night ..
A little more.
With Russian friends with music up to four in the morning...
Dance danced.
Dance daddy  Dance is great.
Dance is great.
You should do me something If she finds out Shaker....  It will be very angry.
- Really?
What happened to Shaker?
What the hell is this?
Uh...
paws...
Sunny...
It'll be here immediately.
Get more  Shut up.
- Not right?
Son of Me, now.
OK.
Good good.
go.
But I'm coming back.
Who is it?
My cousin.
Full powdery.
Shakir tells something when she says.
She's a little girl.
I need her number and address.
Do not worry.
The problem is solved, not to stun it.
Sorry, sir ..
- Yes.
Are you here?
Yes why?
Do you know the spouse and his wife, Nahu?
Is Songkockers?
Sixth floor
- Yes, sir  Their daughter ..
When did you see him finally?
Did she have a daughter?
Actually, there's one apartment on one floor.
So we will never know each other.
Not one. Who are you?
Yes, so.
Have you seen this, Sunny?
Speak  Your daughter's daughter was abducted two months ago.
I want to know about it.
Who are you, cop?
Uh, I'm reading a newspaper editor.
So what?
- I am my principal ..
Oh, Ronnie.
How long I am chasing after
Who am I...
= සූки
- How are you?
What happened?
- Did you get your hair?
I am in the army.
Actually .. it's been cut down.
Yes.
My appearance is?
Mmm...
You are exactly like a bridegroom.
exactly what the friend said.
This is your friend's marriage today.
Keep it safe
That's where the bride is.
Your name.
You're wasting ..
Hey, Warren  O .. or .. Ronnie...
How are you?
How did Ronnie?
You remember a lot ..
How are you?
Let's have fun.
This is Suki's sneezing.
You gotta get married for a few moments.
It was each getting married, Ronnie and Neha.
So suki.
No, no. I was just trying to tell you Ronnie, we'll be right back  I'm not coming anywhere.
I love Nehda, sir.
Say the word  Neha.
Neha.
This is my mom's wedding sari.
Get married?
I can not see you.
Oh oh, it's harder to cope more.
Naha you have a call
- Who?
Hello.
Ronnie needs to go.
Neha.
What has happened?
You just stay here, come here,
- Listen.
Sorry.
Give a second.
Yes - Do not hack up the phone.
I want to hear what's going on there.
Well
Third phase.
No, no, you will not get excited.
Six months ago, an investigation revealed.
Are you married?
Sorry.
I'm drunk
Thank you  Sorry.
Sorry, sir, your purse  You've already come.
But sir if he comes back to the police...
Sorry, sir.
Abductions two months ago No, sir, I do not know anything about it  These cameras should see the images  Here it is
Give seven screenshots  Here sir
Three-hour screenshot is missing.
Do not know, sir ..
How to disappear.
The three hours of the screenshot that went into the abduction. Where are they?
How can it happen?
Yes, sir, one day the police came.
Boss sent us home early.
Picture on the previous day.
Do you know where the lost photos are?
Sir, all these videos can be found in Boss' cabin.
Can I see them in?
It's a bit difficult sir, but you can do it
As I meet, I want to make calls on my own.
Well, of course, sir  This sir.
Who is this beggar?
Hey. It's our new AKP. Sir
But why are so many creeps for her?
Good morning, sir  Morning.
- Welcome to cabbage.
Sharith Kutay ..
screw......  (crate is a dog)
- fluff
Envelope
'Koo' will be extended.
Or it's a big deal.
Carbon ..
How was Carney G?
Parent name .. Is it for spiritual protection?
Rane ..
- Good.
Sir, this is your personal partner, Bosco  Oh... yes... Yes... Bosco ..
Yes, sir.
What of your stomach so much?
Sorry, sir.
Do this. From tomorrow morning...
Walk with me ten miles [10 km].
Good?
Well, sir.
Well, I'm... Sir...  Bosco
What do the people of the department say about me?
Nothing, sir.
Do not you say anything?
I do not say anything
- Something said  Say... tell me
Sir, this is ..
Everyone tells you the antidote.
Do you speak the gonor?
She ..?
No, sir.
The robot is telling me ..
- No sir Who says?
You tell me?
Sorry, sir.
What do you mean?
- No sir.
Who says?
Take the number.
What are you crying boss?
I made a joke...
It's gone...
- Sir, Mr. DIG is calling you.
HAHHH.
These are the seniors. Are they always eating us?  Sir.
Come In...
Loha Singhul .. or LSD
Welcome to cabbage.
Police are talking about you a lot.
Sit down... sit down...
Your name is very interesting What's the secret...?
There's a sermon in that... that...
If you're in Rome...... be like a Roman  I was living with a rowdler, so I thought to be like that.
Sometimes, sir.
Yes, yes It's time to drag on a path  See the LSD gentlemen.
The day you spend is correct.
But the system is very wrong.
My method is my identity, sir.
Because it's not there
LSD yesterday I killed three people.
If you do not kill people, how can you put a sixty-five incumbent record?
Fifty five Sir, it's... working  Besides the thieves, did you even spy on the police?
Sorry Sir
- see LSD
How about...
I'll take care of Watch out... ... your image...  Do not look like your coat If you want to learn ..
How Much Learn...
Name how purely it is, even if there are ten non-tasking activators...
Apology was received.
A record has been broken down...
Honor is increased.
No, no, sir.
It would have to be a cellfriend if you remember  Sir ..
Wait a little  Get lost too  Get it, sir.
result.
Do not worry, sir.
They bring the flying up and down.
I see cabbage hatching...
Congratulations.
How to?
UMCan?
Why are you coming after us?
I'm looking for a little girl.
I do not know about any little girl.
But I can show you a big girl.
Stop ..
Stop...
Where is Rai?
I do not know about "Ria."  I want to know where Ria is?
- I do not know anything  Right.
Hey Sagger.
Who are those Russians?
Oh, they are.
An address was asked from me.
Do you give so much money saying an address?
Please, bro.
Not without people like that  Get it Hyde ..
Or I'll get it Do you know the child?
It's a brooch.
This cabbage ..
I've been selling a lot of drugs ..
Good.
If I make a mistake .. I also have it.
You are a very ordinary man.
What does it involve?
These are big big games.
If you have a little step in advance...  Imagine what would happen.
The Usman step left.
Two are done.
Hey...
- Are you mad?
Are you mad?
Two men come to 20
He was not looking for you ..
He has been picked up by me.
Next time  You're going to be ready to die  Let's go  He is my responsibility...
What do you want?
Why are they fighting against them?
I'm looking for this baby  It was abducted two months ago.
Do you know about him, have you ever seen her?
What do you see here?
Did you think that you are holding a mantissa?
I am the owner of the hire.
That's where this is.
I do not know  or stop these.
Do not fight in the black rook
Stop it.
I'm sorry for you  It's about me.
Ucman You know me from 4 days
I have known this child for four years.
Imagine how sad I was about her.
Busy
- Sorry  THUNDER?
I'm sorry last night.
I was a bit more.
I think I did not read much more.
No, that's okay.
Can I get my card back?
Sorry, maybe it's a mistake.
Actually there are some things like that  This is yours.
This is mine.
Oh, no, it will not open the door.
Thank you.
- I'm Ananda's Buddha.
= Lucknow police...
Captain Ranwer Pratap Singh. Nice to meet you...
Oh, it's amazing.
Fun will have two things.
Army, police.
Come on. Tell about the army,
I will tell you about the police.
Sorry, I'm sorry. ♥ I'm tired.
Well. Let's eat dinner soon.
Get it
- Then ..
Room Service
- Good afternoon sir. Your dinner.
Uh...
Looks like you do not like police guys Hmm?
But good night.
- Hmm ..
- Sir ..
I'm in the press. I'm in the arena.
I came to take the photo.
What's wrong with Ronnie
is an advertisement for the newspaper.
If there are people involved in this incident,
will answer this.
But Schrack returns today. What is he saying to her?
I do not have any answers to all your problems  And believe me.
In the same way, wait a little longer.
So.
Have you read the newspaper today?
Check who check.
Find out if I have any information.
I have all the information
But I'll find the money. Would you meet me by check?
Thank you.
It's very busy, Captain, sir  Sorry.
Calling again what to do?
Why to go to war with all the time!  If you have any information, you will get money.
Sir, I do not need money.
I want to know...
Will I have my daughter?
Send your address.
I'll meet you there.
- Uh... Mr. darie
I went to Mumbai six months ago.
In the meantime... Our Ria disappeared.
I was looking for a lot.
Not at all
Complaints to police...
But there is no result.
First Sunday ..
See a picture.
How do you know Ria?
Why is Rea...?
Where did you get these photos?
I took all of you pictures.
I have more pictures at home.
I'll get it if you want.
Ria is your daughter?
- Sure, my daughter.
If you do not tell the truth, you will find yourself in your house.
I even have a birth certificate.
What...?
Look here
This is the birth certificate This is the complaint of the Mumbai Police Station.
My daughter disappeared in Mumbai.
Why are you looking for cabbage?
Yes ..
- Hello.
Ispectricus?
Yes ..
- Shekar is speaking.
Neha's husband.
you made an advertisement in the newspaper about a disappearance.
Yes.
I want to meet you right now.
Can I come to my office?
I will come back.
Please, please.
The blue jeans.
Blue shirt.
Gift.
Lucknow police.
Lucknow police in cabbage.
Could be cautious...
Anand Shaikh.
Crime Section...
Lucknow police: Why here for cabbage?
A friend's marriage is on.
Your Commissar Sir, I know.
Do you know?
Yes, well.
- great
Let's talk to him.
Shiker. How's the friend?
After a long time.
It's because you remembered.
How are you? - I'm fine
It's not...
Do you know Ananda's grandmother?
Gift.
- Uh, yeah. Lucknow police.
Yes, yes. Yes, I'm vacant.
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
Yes I have it.
Are you talking to him?
- All right.
Nice.
You will receive a call from the Minister.
Looks like busy sir.
cut.
How do you know Nhh?
Oh, at the restaurant.
Normal friends. He said Riah is missing.
Help me.
Then you're our neighbor  Sustavi was heard.
Yes. Nehma Madam ..
No tip has been received.
So I wanted to see what I wanted.
I have come here this morning ..
I saw your ad at the time
I was really surprised
- I'm sorry "I was surprised" How I tell you how  We do not have a daughter.
What?
- Yes.
We do not have any daughter.
HAHH... But...
- On February 7th.
Neha's car robbery ..
It's a car robbery.
They had beaten her hard.
And Shakir.
- Ten days were commenced.
Neha.
How are you?
Thank God for your mindfulness.
I was very upset...
Where is Ria?
What action?
Since he has regained his consciousness
I talked about a child.
asked people where our raria is.
Have you seen our Russia?
- not..
Did you see my daughter, Anna?
- No ..
They were playing at the building.
- Neha...
What are you doing this...?
- Not only that.
A notice of a missing child in a foreign newspaper was seen.
I had a phone call and told me that this is our opera.
She was very upset.
It was very difficult ..
Neha please open the door.
Are you crazy?
We had a daughter, Shaikh.
- We did not have a daughter  We had a daughter, Shaikh.
- We did not have a daughter.
He was sick while he was waiting.
PTST
post traumatic stress disorder
(post-traumatic stress disorder) Is it still?
- Yes.
Actually.
We had to have an abortion
Nahi was always hoping that his mother would be his daughter.
Because of Naih's baby, his mother was gone.
And then...
This danger has changed all of us.
Come on. I'll show you every photo of Ria.
There is no photo.
What happened to Ria's photos?
Every room was left.
MY YOUR OWN RYAJA.
And Ria's favorite clothes in the cottage here  Ever since, do I explain to you that we have no daughter?
All of our pictures are here
_ Where are they now?
We do not have a daughter
- Where did she go? Where is Ria?
This nonsense has gone further Next, he went to the police ..
= The complaint was made to the child where the missing person is
I was just taking my child to school while I was leaving
A lot came. They took my daughter
I do not know how to find him All the police suspected me before.
But later they understood...
They are... lying after lying  What is really ..
We did not have any daughter Ria  You mean...
All this... imagined in Naīa?
You are a police officer?
He met you in a normal way?
Ronnie. My ..
Neha
- Hahh What kind of speech did you say to your friend.
No such thing happened
You got the wrong information
I'm sorry, Shaker.
Mumbai...
Please do not do this again
It's fire in my mind...
More info...
You understand.
I already have a lot of trouble.
Sir, I watch the watchman's house at school
CCTV scores
_ Come on You do not have a photo on the car or you do not have a phone or a home
Principel says that no kid was in school named Riah
I asked a newspaper asking me a question.
= Shekker sent the message.
Police stopped investigating because you were wrong
Nobody has seen a daughter in school
No police station, Princess, No one knows
I saw CCTV eyes with I robbed me There's no one there you are  He was hiding behind the seat behind Ronnie.
Your
_ - She was scared  They are not your daughter but the car.
I came to Sheikher now.
You did not have a daughter.
Please trust me, Ronnie How to believe?
You give the child in the photo and say that he is someone else  Everyone is lying, Ronnie.
And you?
Did you tell me the truth for so long?
How to say how I say  I was scared.
Four years after you spoke to you ..
Nobody believes me.
Everybody says I'm crazy
You do not believe me, do you?
Close your eyes See if you can see who you are.
My daughter...  Ria ..
Ria is here.
What is your mother's name?
Ria
- There is no other man outside her but your life
You are changing Rya...
your mother was thinking of coming to your daughter.
You have an abortion, Neha.
You did not have a baby  You did not have a baby  go.
Neha
Ronnie Ronnie here  Neha City...
Let me alone.
Let me alone. Please  Highlight on height  Tell me the truth then?
Ria.
Neha.
Highlights on the...
Tell me the truth then?
Neha.
I found Shekcher.
You have no daughter.
Everyone is lying, Ronnie.
You are changing Rya...
your mother was thinking of coming to your daughter.
You have an abortion, Neha.
You did not have a baby.
Please trust me, Ronnie  Neha...
Sir
Is this here?
- Yes, sir
Is this the husband?
- Yes Sir...
Who is this?
- Your lame ..
Is not it?
I suspected me too ..
But I'm a cop.
Drinking cigarettes is harmful to health.
It's like this.
Mmmm....
From here?
Is it pushed?
She ..?
Say...
What time is the Bosco time?
- Three forty minutes, sir  Seen...
How fast is the answer.
You are saying so.
Tell me, or do you want to hurt?
I have to call my lawyer.
What the hell is this?
Do you want to have a smartphone and get smart?
d.
just throwing up the phone,
You did not even throw anything...
Seating.
Say...
How did these things happen?
I came from Canada this morning.
- Bosco - Yes, sir
Take the flight list.
- All right, sir.
Why did you go to Canada?
My second office is mine.
If the second office...
What caused your wife to be pushed?
Find out what you should look for.
I lost my wife
Who do you have here...?
Nobody answers
- Bosco - yes sir  First lie.
Your brother came.
Sunny.
Has he pushed too hard?
She can make it.
My little brother is mine.
Very common guy.
Bosko's second lie.
- Yes, sir
A powdered asshole.
- Yes sir A drug is never normal.
Look, mister.
If this is your brother, this has been done... Give it to us Vah Bosco.
Both of you have to practice sleeping in the cement.
Why do not prisoners have bed...
open your ears and ask...
Your brain...
Home bell...
and phone...
Keep it constantly.
Or I'll turn you off forever.
I will be smart too.
We have a bosco.
What do you think, sir? Does he tell the truth?
I was looking for his own lame.
Got it?
It's a lone liar. That asshole.
But she is not killed.
- It means ..
A suicide case
- No, bun.
The color of this case is too long to wait.
Bosco ..
- Yes sir How long is the date?
Three, three, sir ..
Then three, three, thirteen, thirteen... How much?
- Thirty-nine sir ..
- No, honey
Three, Three, Three, Thirteen '
This CCTV camera does not know how to work ..
- Work, sir.
No, I do not care.
Let's see what it looks like Sir, this is the Nehru Sunglocker phone.
Do it.
Give this to Bosco
I would like to receive incoming calls, calls, watsup, snapshot, facebook
A married woman, Neha Songolkkar, has committed suicide by jumping off a sixth floor.
sources say...
Ria is my everything
I need your help  No one helped me in the last two months
I am not selfish;
I'm helpless.
= Roberts, Ronnie, help me find my daughter.
Four years after you spoke to you ..
Nobody believes me.
Everybody says I'm crazy
You do not believe me, do you?
Family members say that Neha Sangolcker was in some form of depression.
Sir, this is Neha Madame's call list
The last call was taken to Ranwer Prathap Singh
her address was found.
Wahh Bosco .. Wah
- Okay, sir?
Did you find you?
- Yes sir  Then you ask me why this is right or wrong?
Sorry, sir. - Sorry, sir?
Do not know, sir ..
What do not you know? Is this right?
- Yes, sir
Then what is it?
- Sorry, sir...
I made a joke by Bosco ..
Pleas ..
Do not cry.
Are you so sensitive?
This is what you came for?
- Yes sir  Well, this is right.
This can get us a criminal.
go
- All right, sir.
Sir. This is Ranweer Prithaphon Singh, I know.
How to?
One Sunday came with Naha  She was down the street ..
Why did you break up your show?
Sir, not that, broke it?
Two teats and four cups broken.
It was not easy to tame.
Sir, I got surveillance CCTV.
But it's clear, sir.
Then, send in one Chandigarh and explain it very clearly.
Young.
What is the horror of Ranvir Prathap?
The autopsy report indicates that this is suicide, and the police also approve it.
Hello, Sagge.
- Let's talk about Usman later  Sallier ..
you .. day ..  showed a picture of a child, right?
photo...?
If I had told you the truth...
Nah Ma'am was alive today.
UMC
How do you know Nhh?
- I do not know Naihama.
But I know everyone else is lying Nay Ma'am is not crazy.
Everything is said to be true.
A few days ago, I went to Sunny.
Talk about my next deal.
There.
Hello, Sweetie.
Do you?
Take the bag
The next deal...
Ajaud.
Eight
- and
This is for you
- Now go.
Get out of here.
I told you to
tell me to come.
You two hours early. - There's no place to keep him  By myself.
I saw him.
A child
- Hey.
It's a mouthpiece.
or close forever. Got it, right?
I was scared, Sagger, so lied
But I did not know that my lie would ruin anyone's life.
He was looking for his daughter like a madman.
Everyone in front is crying aloud...  No one believed.
I am loyal to you, Sagge...
you will do me whatever you like
But the baby needs to be saved.
Is Ria alive?
I do not know that...
It can be said that is Sunny ..
- Where can I see Sunny...?
Uh... I can tell.
There you can see a kid, right?
Anand Shaikh.
I will kill him.
Before I came to know that I was not.
Take me to Sunny.
Come on...
God bless you Who is killed?
You have killed the wrong person.
Hello! - Ranveer Prithar Singh?
Who is this ..?
- LSD
Loha Singh Dul cabbage police...
That's not the guy I'm saying.
Where is...
in the hotel ..
There I will come and see you.
We're coming.
Who asked?
Cabbage Police
- She... Cabbage Police
Now ..?
- Sunny...
"Muhini"
"Ding... Dong... Dong..."
"Ding... Dong... Dong... Dong... Dong... Dong..."
"Ding... Dong... Ding... Dong...."
"One..."
"Two..."
"Three..."
"Four..."
"Five..."
"Six..."
"Seven..."
"Eight..."
"Nine..."
"Ten..."
=>    Eleven...
"Twelve..."
"Thirteen..."
"One..."
"Two..."
"Three..."
"Four..."
"Five..."
"Six..."
"Seven..."
"Eight..."
"Nine..."
"Ten..."
Eleven...
"Twelve..."
"Thirteen..."
=>    "Your future...."
"I was picking you up for the day..."
<span style = "font-size:
"Come in Spring Spring is here..."
"Ding... Dong... Dong..."
"Ding... Dong... Dong... Dong... Dong... Dong..."
"Dong... Dong... Dong..."
"Come on, I'll live together..."
""
"How many more are there..."
"We both have been drunk"
"And I know.
<span style = "font-size:
"Ding... Dong... Dong..."
"You received a message on the fourteenth day..."
"It was there on the 15th day."
<p style = "text-
So, how are you? ..
For the Thousand Days...
"When you are ready for the next..."
<span style = "font-size:
"I was picking you up for the day..."
"Come in Spring Spring is here..."
"Ding... Dong... Dong..."
"Ding... Dong... Dong... Dong... Dong... Dong..."
"Dong... Dong... Dong..."
Hey, one, two, three, "
One, two, three, "
One, Two, Three,
"I broke my heart on the 18th day"
"In the twentieth day, I've lost twenty hearts..."
"Come in Spring Spring is here..."
"Ding... Dong... Dong..."
"Ding... Dong... Dong... Dong... Dong... Dong..."
"Dong... Dong... Dong..."
"Ding... Dong... Dong..."
"Ding... Dong... Dong... Dong... Dong... Dong..."
"Dong... Dong... Dong..."
Hey ..
Where is Ria? Who are you?
Where is Ria?
Sunny...
Where is he going?
Say
- They both run away.
There I go.
It's crazy.
It looks like you're in the city. The way you are in the field is that you have to change.
Did you say to the hotel?
I was sitting in the room to do a cloth?
Does it tell Reia to die?
Nahtaradee Naaha's life was lost.
All this is pathetic.
You were there, did you?
Yes, you were where you went and kidnap his daughter  Huh?
Read more ..
stuffed into the prison cell .. ..
_ Ugly mouths to wake up...
Only cages and cords can only be...
Use the uniform to protect the people, for so long?
Oh, soldier...
A little leaflets.
You got my officers to hit your teeth, did not you?
You think that the whole police department was attacked?
How big will it cost you...
You are stubborn. Will melt and flow.
You always tie your hands and put your body in your cages...
Give one chance ▶ Show the strength of a soldier.
Let's see where we go  We will meet your will.
Get it off.
leave it ..
Drop it.
Both go back.
How low you are all Hey, you.
No.
Why should I get upset?
It's not a time of inquiry.
I had the time to touch them.
Meaning
- Meaning Sunny.
That kidnapping is behind
Why do not query?
evidence?
evidence ..?
- I have evidence.
Is this Ronnie real?
Have you seen that you have a place in Sanny's place?
Uthman do not worry
Nothing happens.
Tell the truth. What did you see?
I left for Sunny.
I saw a kid there.
- Good.
Can you just tell ya at your court (in court)?
Coat, what can I say?
No, no.
Can I say this at court?
- Hahh. - Well, then.
This is your responsibility to court.
Take the sunny.
And this is Sunny.
Yes, sir.
- Look at it.
sir bugger
I'll take care of it  I'll see.
I will do so. Please
Hello, Sunny.
Salgunkar.
Now you tell me to tell...
"Everything that says truth is only true. I do not say anything else but truth."
No, it's old now.
Only in films are they going.
I ask only one question.
The only one.
Where is Ria?
Sunny
What action?
DIG sir does not know who she is dealing with Your son's son.
Your donkey, he is Is he?
Oh, really .. Ria...
- Ahh Give one minute.
Ria... Ria ..
Where is Ria?
If you look, you will find the puck.
Check?
Is this a question for asking questions?
Just ask if you ask.
Sunny. Careful, careful.
Hey DIG ..
- Hmm ..
Do not smoke?
- Say where Rii was initially.
Do not Know - Sunny Sunny  I do not know.
I told you I did not know.
I will not leave you
now say
Now let's go. Or it's okay to
_ go back.
This is very dangerous
_ The way things are heard is very different.
I'm talking...
Stay back.
- No
Do not move.
Do not move, sir.
Put the gun on the side.
- Hey, Hey!
I know
you will kill me
I do not even save any of you.
Close your mouth I'm going to kill both of you.
Get down, Sunny.
Remove the gun
Go back
- Shut up.
You can not die.
Suny, you can not die.
Sunny...
Ronnie. Those are not good.
The situation was out of control.
You have to control your temper.
I want revenge.
It's not the job of the police to revenge, Ronnie.
The police work law enforcement.
You told me that he was suing Naomi because he could not find his daughter.
Nobody cares.
Nobody cares. No one
Is happiness in these faces?
Smiling, happy faces.
My second anniversary is the day.
I was driving.
An accident.
My older brother.
My wife.
His child was eight months old.
Everybody lost.
The loss they lost.
And loneliness ..
I know both well.
It's a lot of love, is not it?
Gee, this is not your life.
That life gave me daddy.
I found in the nose college.
This is his last request. (Last Will)
She's dying Ronnie.
We were married.
Look at the dad's condition.
Can not say no.
I do not have anyone else, Ronnie.
Shaker.
How did Shaikh come?
In two days, Shaikhar and I will adore it.
What will happen to me?
I have to go.
I can not live without you.
You will not be able to forgive me...
But I have to try to forget.
Going Ronnie.
Sir ..
Farm House has come up with goods.
Give the golden
gold  Goldfish.
Sorry.
I send a photo  Well, just go Only Sunny was aware of where the child was.
Sir, I have no battles with Sheikker.
But I know he knows the truth.
Sir, arrest him...
I promise everything will work right.
Only one can not arrest a person
We do not have any proof.
Well.
One more question.
This girl has four years old boyfriend...
I remember all the memories he has with him.
How he is forgotten ..
He has a kid or not.
Ronnie: I can understand what you are saying.
But I just have to say...
Do not just sit wrong...
If so, you... this case...
will be both annoying.
If Colonel Ranjit comes in...
can you imagine right now?
I do not know who my department is involved in.
LSD, hurt, or somebody else.
Give me about twelve hours.
I'll take this case to the best place and go.
Trust me.
UMC.
- Ronnie  Usman
Uh... Uh-Uh
What happened with Usman ..
Uh... I... I... uh... no... no....
= Usman .. Usman...
U.S. ..
My time is Ronnie.
- Do not say that, Uthman.
Do not say that. Please.
U.S. ..
I will send a photo Where is Geoffrey?
Indigenous borders...
In the middle of a forest of ten acres... When the Chattanooga River crosses...
The river is... an armed force...
It has the protection of the entire army...
There is Geiger's dwelling
Tell him that his goods will be heading for the shipyard tomorrow...
Bye.
Quiet.
Do not take a wrong move...
Or you... This case...
will be both annoying.
You need control over anger
Do you love him a lot?
I do not know who my department is involved in.
I'm shy about my officers.
Think Colonel Ranjith comes here  You should trust me ..
Once a soldier will always be a soldier.
Hold it.
Sir, he entered the jungle...  The strength of a soldier can not be overcome.
It will not work...
Come to the reefs.
Colonel Sir
- Officer ..
Did Captain Ranveer know anything about it?
Not yet known, but we are looking for him.
But if we get caught...
imagine that you have gone up...
But if you explain to her...
Maybe... He will survive his life.
You are misplaced and misled by the officer I did not understand him or save her.
I came to save her from you.
This joke, right?
In his home...
If you enter it,  He will show you the hell...
In the war, there's nothing to lose her...
And it will not be left on your...
He represents himself an army...
You should be careful  I am asking briefly, Colonel sir.
I promise... the first bullet...
I have...
Congratulations on your heart... !!!!
Give me the gun...  Call the gravel...
Calling gravel...
Sir, you can not stop him  Get Machines... Call Alfa One
_ What's wrong with anyone?
Hello... Call the Rangers Is not one or none?
Sir, he came in to the Farm House...
There was a lame daddy you ..?
Dad will forget another dream... You know, my older brother says...  It reads very much
I killed it ..
No, I told you.
You said no ..?
What do you want?
Ria...
- It's alive.
More?
Ria... Ria... Ria...
If I do not ask, what do I need?
I am from the government employment.
I needed one chance...
Find money.
I suddenly torched
I met ..
Riaia ..
Sunny  Anne .. DIG sir  Today ..?
- Holiday today ..
Why the uproar?
What is it, sir? Where is the goods?
Good in the day.
- All right, sir.
What's that noise?
- Sir, do not shoot.
No Sir
I'm going to know the real story...
Picking up to Shacker...
Is this your brother?
one job... Can not you fix it?
Meaning
- Meaning ..
The things that have become so...... occurred under my consent ..
Under your knowledge...?
It does not fill the stomach for money  But when I arrived...
The heart fills up...
Other is my heart too big ..
You misbehave with the child...
I do not know them and have no relevance  Now listen to what's relevant to me  My life's most important deal...
Sheiker was a shipping company ..
Only Shakespeare could do my job.
It's such a big thing .. It's going to be a big ship ..
Come next at least in the least two months ..
- Okay.
I will wait for two months
Then I will have your hostage  is alive...
I promise.
You do my job...
I'll do your job.
But if something goes wrong then my brother will be both good...
The comrades of Salgonkar
_ are in jail for ever...
promise.
I hate her to his wife...
I made her mad  no abduction was there ..
He wanted to kill him.
Where is Ria?
- What did you do?
I did not want to kill Ria ..
Shakir wants shakers... Sheker totally destroyed Riah's mind.
Doctors say that Na'a can not open her anxiety.
We need to have no daughter to control it.
My daughter I lost...
My wife will not lose me
-Sheiker But this is wrong.
your lie is a lie. My family can be protected.
Please help me.
I can not live without my wife.
I can not live without my lair  Well ..
Salgoncker: We are with you  He helped me...
so I helped him ..
Will be there for more?
-
School welfare
Thank you, ma'am.
Thank you.
you delete ..
Finished.
- Let's go.
Curly .. - Yes Sir
- Close this case.
There is no trace in this.
I'm talking.
Hear it. Her method is so different.
Take my gun from my waist  Calm down.
I arrived...
So I had to finish it.
Not every war is won by strength...
For the brain won.
Everything you did was pretty good...
But the wrong child was chosen...
chosen child...
Ria is my last...
I need your help.
They kidnapped my daughter
your eyes to see who can see...
Ria...
Go back...
Back to... Back...
Cabbage, Claire Sir...
Good Enjoy...
You can not die that way.
Get up
Get up.
- Sir
You can not die like that -
Rise up. Ranveer...
Ronnie ..
No, sir, the gunman can not die...
I can not die like that...
- I know that child...
The war is over.
I can not die.
- I know kids ..
The helpless child, Ria sir...
The first bullet was right there, Colonel Sir...
The last one is dead
How can you be my friend ..
Three years old child...
It's yours...
let's say...
If not my daughter ...
child of another...
I have dad..
Now you understand that...
Why did not you want to find Roya...
the time we were together was the most beautiful thing in life
It will always be remembered...
Then Ria was my last one
You can not forgive me...
But you have to try to forget ..
neha
Do not go to naha Please
I love you
I love you  I'm sorry
Ready to see her?
my daughter
riya
hi
Where is Mamma...?
Are we going to Mom?
come on bosko
Take a car...