Every moment of your life is a test,
one that reveals who you are.
And if you truly
are worthy of the name Zod,
you will follow
in the footsteps of those
who have come before you.
Or you will die trying.
If you didn't know
Brainiac had corrupted
the Voice of Rao,
then why even attempt a coup?
Because Daron-Vex
offered to spare your life
in exchange for my help.
- Stop!
- And I would do it again.
Hello, Father.
I came to tell you...
that I forgive you
for what you tried to do to me.
Black Zero is in.
They want something in return.
There he is. My old friend, Daron-Vex.
We have a lot of catching up to do.
Ona!
What's wrong?
Through fire, we are reborn.
I learned of a pre-cataclysm instrument
of violence so powerful
it would give even Brainiac pause.
That thing in there,
they told me it's called Doomsday.
If you let that thing loose
it will kill everything
that it comes across.
It's true.
That's why we have given over our lives
to protecting the universe
from Doomsday.
[painful whines]
[sighs]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
What does this alien want?
To rip this city right from the ground
and add it to his collection.
You didn't really think
the Voice of Rao was a god, did you?
Why kill the chancellor? And the others?
All I can say is there's going to be
a lot more bodies if we don't find him.
Look...
I can't risk being up here any longer.
Just have you Sagitari...
You mean what's left of the Sagitari?
They're already spread too thin.
The remains of the Council
are either dead or in hiding.
The Primus has turned traitor.
Black Zero is openly
walking the streets.
I can't help you.
[overlapping chatter]
Do us a favor and go back inside.
It's not safe out here. Go on! Move!
- [gun clicks]
- Whoa.
It's chaos out there.
I know. And it's getting worse.
Pretty soon people
are going to figure out
that no one's in charge.
Then the whole city is going
to descend into anarchy.
Making it even harder to find the Voice.
Three days of searching and nothing.
Nyssa said they found a trail
of mangled bodies
leading out of the Tower of Justice.
She's there now.
She's trying to find out more.
Brave of her.
We need to find him, Lyta.
We need to find him
and stop him
from bringing Brainiac here.
We will.
And we'll make him pay
for what he's done.
[soft dramatic music]
How's Dev?
I-I managed to get him in a med bay.
He's recovering.
Itching to get back in the fight.
Good.
[sighs] We're going to need him.
And a whole lot more just like him.
Seg...
I know losing Ona was hard for Kem,
but sending him to Kryptonopolis...
Was that to help him or to help you?
I'm worried you're starting to think
this fight we're in,
that maybe we can't win it.
♪ ♪
Is that what you think?
Everything that Adam said...
about my grandson, about the Els,
about who we are...
who we're meant to be.
He believed that
I could save the universe.
I couldn't even save him.
I've lost too many people already, Lyta.
I can't lose anyone else.
You're not going to lose me.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[panting]
[grunting]
You cannot stop me.
I am coming for you and your world.
[painful screams]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
That's a lot of hardware.
The Voice of Rao is wounded.
And like all wounded animals,
this is when they are most dangerous.
No one's seen him. He's in hiding.
It's not him we're going after.
The fall in the Genesis Chamber
didn't kill the Voice.
The only way to fight something
that cannot be killed
is with a weapon that is unkillable.
We're going to get Doomsday?
[panicked breaths]
Look how far you've fallen, old friend.
[scoffs]
The same could be said for you,
Sela-Sonn.
How does one transition...
from one of the most respected
and highly regarded members
of the Science Guild,
protégé of the great Val-El, no less,
to leader of an insurgency
whose only currency
is death and destruction?
It started with a betrayal.
From someone I trusted.
You think I didn't know?
That you'd covered your tracks so well
I wouldn't follow them back to you.
That's no excuse.
You dedicated your life to saving lives.
Not destroying them.
That was a long time ago.
And all my work trying
to ease people's suffering
gave me keen insight
into how to inflict it.
I have a lot of questions
for you, Daron,
and I intend to get answers.
[painful screams]
And my name is Jax-Ur now.
[scattered chatter]
Lyta's disappeared.
So has Zod.
With far more firepower
than one man can handle
and with one of Black Zero's skimmers.
They're going for Doomsday.
To think you were all expecting me
to screw you guys over.
[dramatic music swells]
♪ ♪
I realize this wasn't easy for you.
Going against Seg.
And I understand
why you admire his idealism.
But ideals are no good to the dead.
It was sheer luck that he survived
that blast in the tavern.
Get to the point.
It's up to us to save him
and everyone else.
And the only way we can do that
is by making the hard choices.
Even ones as extreme
as unleashing Doomsday.
But how can we be sure?
You said Doomsday
is a genetically engineered
killing machine
that can't be controlled.
He functions like any apex predator.
Focusing on the most
formidable opponent first.
- That's Brainiac.
- Great.
And after that, he'll work his way
down the food chain.
That's us.
Before that happens,
we return him to stasis.
We're risking a lot on
being able to pull that off.
That's Seg talking.
Don't think of this as a betrayal.
You and I, we're Zods.
Duty-bound to protect our people
by any means necessary.
Seg's an El.
He will never understand that.
But at least he'll be alive
to forgive you.
[ground rustles]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
So how are you planning
on getting inside?
I'd like to know that, too.
'Cause all that firepower isn't
going to get you in there.
You need a Zod and an El.
And I won't do it.
I don't need you to.
Lyta, you once asked
if I knew who my father was.
At the time, I didn't.
But I do now.
House of Zod...
House of El.
You're both. You're my son.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Where is it?
Seg, if you know something...
Doomsday is already
far beyond your reach.
I've made sure of that.
You knew.
It was your mother who convinced me.
She knew that Zod would come for it.
I just never thought
that you'd help him do it.
You couldn't have moved it far.
- I will find it.
- You like to believe
you're a few steps ahead, General.
But it turns out I know these
tunnels better than you do.
How else do you think we beat you here,
when you snuck away
in the middle of the night?
Then you have sealed Krypton's fate.
Careful.
Seg, come in.
Go ahead.
We have a problem.
- [high-pitch whirring]
- [painful screaming]
Admit it, Daron.
Admit what you did
and this pain will end.
I didn't do anything.
- [high-pitch whirring]
- [painful screams]
Exactly.
I trusted you.
I told you of my fears
and you did nothing.
You were the one who
restored the Codex technology.
What did you think was going to happen?
- [high-pitch whirring]
- [painful screams]
Without my work on the Codex,
the Genesis Chamber
would have become unsustainable
and we would have lost
our only means of reproduction.
Well, if your intentions
were so noble...
why is you work shrouded
in such secrecy?
Because I knew
that in the wrong hands it could be used
to purify the Guilded bloodlines.
Weed out those viewed as weaker.
Just never could have imagined
you would be the one to betray me.
[dark music]
Back then, the only people I
trusted were you and Val-El.
And when you sentenced him to death...
I knew I was next.
That's not the worst
of it, is it, Daron?
You had to take it one step further.
Yes, I know about the Vara Protocol.
♪ ♪
And now you are going
to tell me how to access it.
- [high-pitch whirring]
- [painful screaming]
[low intermittent pulsing]
Why have we stopped?
What's happening?
[speaking native language]
Raika, what's going on?
The containment field.
It is failing.
What do you mean, failing?
[speaking native language]
He thinks we damaged it
when we moved it.
This is all that keeps the beast inside.
How long do we have?
It is ancient technology.
It could be days or weeks.
Or maybe hours.
One thing is certain,
the beast will break free of his tomb.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
Now I know why, growing up,
my mother never spoke of her mother.
The shame she must have felt.
Your willingness to betray everything
the House of Zod stands for.
I'm fighting for a better Kandor.
You and I can restore order to Kandor.
I reclaim my role
as Primus of the Sagitari,
and with you by my side
we can rebuild our city.
Return it to what it once was.
Not the Kandor he wants to create,
a place ruled by fear!
How can you say that?
All my life all you have done
is make me afraid.
Afraid that I wasn't good enough.
That I wasn't strong enough.
That I wasn't worthy of the Zod name.
I have failed you
in so many ways, Lyta.
I tried to mold you
into a hardened warrior.
Tried to drive out your love for Seg.
Your refusal to follow orders
you disagreed with.
I saw your constant questioning
as a weakness.
And now I see
it's your greatest strength.
Don't lose it now when you need it most.
Because you're going
to have to make a choice.
Grandpa, come in. Do you read me?
Yes. What's wrong?
You weren't by any chance programmed by
real Grandpa with a working knowledge
of ancient Kryptonian
technology, were you?
Like, say, how to repair
the containment field
on a capsule designed
to hold a genetic experiment
gone horribly wrong?
No, but I'd be willing to try.
[dramatic music]
Well, that's confidence-inspiring.
Would you like me to divert my efforts
from determining the proximity
of Brainiac's ship?
Has it arrived in our system yet?
No, but it's only a matter of time.
Then let's concentrate
on problems closer to home first.
Thank you, old friend.
You've been very helpful.
Wait!
There's one more secret
I didn't divulge to your leader.
And what would that be?
One that could make you
one of the richest men in Kandor.
The location of the Voice of Rao's cache
of untraceable solars.
[scoffs] You can't buy me.
Perhaps you just haven't
been offered the right price.
Think of your family.
All that you could do for them.
I have no family.
They died in the Xarxas outbreak.
All the medication
was rationed to the Guilded.
It was not a quick death.
So unless you can bring them back,
you have nothing I could want.
Please. Please.
You have to help me.
Look into your heart. I'm begging you.
You can't let me die here.
No, please!
I'll do anything. Anything!
Just please, please, let me g...
[grunts, groans]
[breathing heavily]
Please! Please!
Please, you can't leave me in here!
Please!
Please, help me.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I can't die here in this place.
Talk to Raika about
the fastest way to the surface.
I'm going to go get the skimmer.
Or we could not do that.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
What are you doing?
It is time for my people
to rid themself of this burden.
We will take the creature to your city.
And risk the lives
of everyone in Kandor?
You can't be serious.
Look, you'll never get it
through the Outlands.
These catacombs contain many secrets.
Even a tunnel to your city.
And when the Collector
of Worlds comes for Kandor,
he will take Doomsday along with it.
And my people will be free
of their duty.
And Krypton will be free of the threat
from that vile creature.
That's not going to happen.
We're going to stop Brainiac.
You cannot even stop your own people
from trying to take the beast.
How will you defeat an alien conqueror?
You will fail, Seg-El.
Listen to me.
If Brainiac is allowed to take Kandor,
then eventually all of Krypton
will be destroyed as a result.
Eventually.
We're guaranteed destruction far sooner
if we do not rid ourself
of this scourge.
[speaking native language]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
You saved my life once.
And for that, I will allow both of you
to leave this place alive.
But try to stop us,
and you will die where you stand.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
I'm done wasting time.
Are you really going to shoot me?
Take one step further and find out.
Then do it.
Better that than
stand here doing nothing
with our planet facing destruction.
Mother stop, please don't do this.
No!
Very well.
You say you intend to restore Kandor
and reclaim your position
as Primus of the Sagitari.
Well, so do I.
Jayna-Zod, I, Dru-Zod,
hereby invoke the spirit of Jo-Mon
and our ancient traditions
in challenging you
to a Kandorian Duel.
For the loser, no mercy will be shown.
I accept.
Mother...
Are you being quiet because
you're coming up with a plan?
The Voice of Rao
is still helping Brainiac
get here to take Kandor...
which now
has a genetically-engineered
killing machine
ready to break free of its cage
somewhere underneath it.
You know,
we could take a skimmer,
make a break for Argo City.
If you're planning on joining
the rapidly swelling ranks
of people screwing me over,
I'd appreciate it
if you just got it over with.
I'm not Lyta.
I believe in you.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Maybe you shouldn't.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[tense music]
You sell skimmers, right?
I want the fastest one you have.
One that won't be picked up
by any of the city scanners.
One that I am prepared
to pay a great deal for.
In fact...
I could make you one
of the richest men in Kandor.
♪ ♪
[soft dramatic music]
Adam should have given
this to someone else.
Instead of giving his life for mine.
But he chose you.
Yeah, well, you met Adam.
Not to speak ill of the dead, but...
he wasn't exactly
the brightest star in the sky.
He picked a guy...
whose only accomplishment
is having a grandson,
who I'll never meet...
Who does something great one day.
Becomes a hero.
Becomes this...
Superman.
Do you know the origins of the El sigil?
[stirring orchestral music]
It comes from
an ancient Kryptonian word.
That means hope.
Our house wasn't just given that symbol.
Our ancestors chose it.
And the generations
to follow defined it.
Not through words...
but through action.
As long as there is an El on Krypton,
there will be hope.
And hope...
can be a powerful weapon.
[both grunting]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[gasping]
[gunshot]
Get away from me.
- How dare you.
- What?
Intervening in a Kandorian Duel.
I saved you.
You stole my honor.
Oh, would you like to be buried with it?
You talk about making hard choices.
Well, I have made one.
Forget her.
We have to go.
What is it?
Daron-Vex escaped.
Fled in a skimmer.
He could be halfway through
Outlands by now.
Ever the survivor.
[high-pitched whirring]
[painful gasping]
[mechanical beeping]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[alarm blaring]
Still can't reach Jayna.
We need to get through to her.
She's the one best suited
to tracking down
the Cythonnites and Doomsday.
And the other problem?
Been thinking about that too.
We never knew why the Voice
was draining power
from the Genesis Chamber.
But I think I know now, and if I'm right
Brainiac will be here sooner
than we thought.
What if he needs it
to power Brainiac's ship?
Bring it here.
He's probably looking
for another source.
But where else would he
get that kind of power?
Grandpa?
There's only one option.
The generator that powers
the city's protective dome.
Then that's where we make our stand.
But we're going to need help.
This could be our last chance
to save Kandor.
You want me to commit
the few remaining Sagitari
we have left to work
alongside terrorists?
Never! They have hunted us,
executed us, forced us underground,
and now you want us to turn
to our oppressors for help,
at the very moment
when we've gained a foothold?
That foothold's about
to be ripped from under you.
And it will happen.
Brainiac is coming
and he will take Kandor.
Unless we declare a truce.
And combine our forces
to put an end
to this threat to our world.
All right, but when this is over
we will round up Black Zero
and take back the city.
We will shatter the Guilds,
strip the ranked of their power,
and we will return Kandor to its people.
Or maybe, instead of both sides
killing each other
we can use this as a chance
to build a better tomorrow.
You sound like your grandfather.
Don't forget which side
had him executed.
[pained breathing]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[gasps]
[echoed footsteps]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[footsteps approaching]
Jayna. Jayna!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[soft dramatic music]
Daron-Vex, manual override.
[electronic beeping]
Passcode: Hantha, Flame-bird, Rokan,
Oregus, two, nine, seven, one, eight.
- [electronic beeping]
- Passcode accepted.
Initiate Vara Protocol.
[electronic whirring]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
What are they?
Clones.
Of the most elite ranked houses.
For what?
So that the people who have everything
can hold onto it.
Forever.
With our combined forces
we can defeat him,
but it will come at a cost.
I know that we all
have our differences here.
But we only have one city
and a common enemy
who wants to take it from us.
So let's work together.
Let's hit the Voice of Rao
with everything that we've got.
I don't take orders from you.
I don't take orders
from you either, or you.
It wasn't so much an order
as a common sense suggestion.
Now you do what you have to do.
But I'm going.
Look, if this goes badly...
and there's every indication
that it will...
I want you to take this.
You go to the fortress, you tell Val
to shut everything down,
and you take that skimmer
to Argo City.
Sure you wouldn't
rather me take a blaster?
I need you to do this.
You're the only one that I can trust.
[stirring orchestral music]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
Unit 1, in position.
Unit 2, in position.
Unit 3, in position.
Let's go.
♪ ♪
Fascinating.
Opposing forces with nothing in common
but their obsession with power.
One hoping to cling to it,
the other to seize it.
Now united...
against me.
But tell me:
does you fear of me
outweigh your fear of each other?
[gun trembling]
- What are you doing?
- It's not me!
I swear!
Whoa! whoa!
Guns down! Guns down! Guns down!
Such weak minds.
Polluted by fear and hatred.
So easily manipulated.
Go on.
You know you want to.
[protesting scream]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
You did what you had to do.
If we don't find Doomsday,
this will all have been for nothing.
Maybe not.
Doomsday was the only way I could see
to destroy Brainiac, but there may be
someone who has another way.
Who?
Val-El.
Val-El died 14 cycles ago.
No, he didn't.
You think I'm responsible for this?
[gasps]
All I did was offer an opportunity
for them to express their truth.
So easy when desire is so strong.
Now come closer.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
Interesting...
that you, a being
of no apparent significance,
are the cause of so much trouble.
A shame.
You would have been quite the prize.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
If I'm being 100% honest,
I really didn't expect that to happen.
You all right?
Shouldn't you be on
that skimmer to Argo City?
[mechanical thrum]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[rustling]
We have to go.
♪ ♪
Krypton.
Your world
is mine.
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com