Previously on Supergirl...
We got rid of two out of
the three Worldkillers.
Ruby Arias must die.
Hi, Patricia.
You were my mother.
And I always wanted
what was best for you.
So you just let me leave?
There's too much at stake for
you to still be mad at me.
I said we would work together.
Never said it would be
sunshine and rainbows.
I'm Guardian.
I broke into your lab for Supergirl.
I trust you.
That wasn't Lex's Kryptonite.
I figured out how to make it.
[JAMES EXHALES]
Wow.
And I thought I had a
nice view from my office.
It's nice waking up with you.
Ever think about getting
your own place?
I mean, you're kinda slumming
it here at the moment.
When I first moved to National City,
I didn't know if I was gonna stay.
Lex was in prison,
the company was in shambles.
I didn't know if I was gonna
put down roots, settle down,
in case the city rejected me.
Well, it's been two years.
I think it's safe to say that
you can sign your own lease.
Even with Supergirl
thinking the worst of me?
- What does she know?
- [CHUCKLES]
Asking you to spy on me?
- What do I know?
- [BOTH CHUCKLE]
I'm really glad I can
tell you my secrets now.
Of course, you can. Me, too.
[LENA GRUNTS]
Where is the child?
Where's Ruby Arias?
[JAMES GRUNTING]
Where is she...
You'll never find her.
[GROANS]
Subtitle sync and corrections by
awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.
[J'ONN J'ONZZ] I went to the
market yesterday, Father.
I bought some of those cocoa beans.
I thought we could mix them up
with some of those Sidamo
Guji beans you like so much.
On this planet, they call the
mixing of the two brown waters...
a mocha.
Please leave me be, Rokar.
It's, uh...
It's not Rokar, it's J'onn, Father.
But I still have a little time
before seeing the Legion off.
But perhaps I could help
you with the Ta'ar Ka'riq,
continue the preservation
of your memories.
I haven't the energy today.
I think it would be good for you.
I have not the energy.
Maybe if you could
turn on the vinyl dis,
that would be nice.
Sure.
Of course.
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING ON RECORD]
[IMRA] Chameleon was the
first Legionnaire to fall.
Stricken by the blade.
Six more quickly followed.
So you put them in stasis
to save their lives.
It was Brainy's idea. Keep them
on ice until we can find a cure.
I was wondering why you hadn't
woken them up to join the fight.
We couldn't risk exposing your
timeline to the sickness.
Couldn't risk causing the very thing
we were trying so hard to prevent.
But we did prevent it.
And with Pestilence
defeated in this time,
they were never infected.
So their vitals are back to normal.
It is imperative that Imra
return to the future.
We don't know that the Titan
Alliance will have held
given the change to the timeline.
Every second we waste could bring
us closer to intergalactic war.
Well, with the Legion's help,
we defeated two Worldkillers.
I think we can handle
Reign from here on out.
Especially with my new cape tricks.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, I guess it's back
to the future then.
Which I do know is a movie title.
I just like saying it.
Mmm. Yes, honestly,
what time traveler doesn't?
"Back... to the future."
[BRAINY] When I first got here,
I assessed you as a
first-level intellect.
Thank you.
As reference, I'm a 12th.
Oh, yes. Yes, you've mentioned that.
But now that I've gotten to know you,
I realize that you're actually
more accurately categorized
as a 1.42-level intellect.
Wow. Thank you.
Mmm. It is I who's expressing
gratitude for all of your help
with this gift.
What's this, space dirt?
Earth dirt.
But it is from the 31st century.
Are you serious? [STAMMERING]
This is future dirt?
Yes.
How did you... Did Mon-El tell
you about my dirt collection?
No, I ran a diagnostic
of your personality,
and calculated with a 98.7% certainty
that you either collected dirt
or New York Mets baseball cards.
And judging by the last 783
uninterrupted Major League seasons,
I figured dirt was more
likely to hold its value.
Shall we embrace?
What are you doing? That's... Oh!
We're gonna bro-hug.
So, this way, and then you wanna...
- Yeah.
- I'll go... Uh...
You... Yeah, that's good. Yeah.
Uh...
[IMRA] The worst moment of my life
was watching my sister die.
But now, because of your help,
I have faith that I'll see her again.
[WINN] Hey, Alex.
You gotta see what Brainy just got me.
Space dirt ain't got
nothing on this baby.
Oh... The nerd-fest beckons.
[LAUGHTER]
[SUPERGIRL] Mon-El's changed a lot.
He's become a great man.
And I'm certain you have
a lot to do with that.
Thanks, Kara.
Hey, [SIGHS] I think
it's time to buckle in.
I'll, uh... I'll help Brainy
with the preparations.
Well, you would think
that we would be experts
at goodbyes now.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
It's no secret that I
struggled when you got here.
Yeah, you weren't the only one.
But I can honestly say now,
truthfully...
I'm really happy I got
to see you again.
Witnessed the man you've become.
It meant the world to me
to be back here with you.
And with everyone.
To fight by your side.
I'm really gonna miss your friendship.
Kara, there's been an
attack at Lena's penthouse.
[EXHALES]
Go.
[WINN] Man, J'onn's gonna
be sad he missed you.
Yeah, tell him it's okay.
I'll see him in a thousand years.
[WINN CHUCKLES]
Okay.
Why would Reign go after Lena?
Well, Lena did imprison
Reign and then, you know,
experimented on her for a little bit.
But revenge isn't Reign's MO.
- I agree.
- [LENA] You're right.
Reign wasn't looking for me.
She was looking for Ruby.
- Is she...
- Reign won't find her.
Ruby's safe, I promise.
And are you okay?
Fine.
So, Reign is after Ruby and
she started with Lena.
Where else might she look?
Sam's mother, Patricia, she's
got a farm outside the city.
Supergirl and I will go
get Patricia to safety
and then wait for Reign to attack.
Anything you've discovered
while studying Reign
that you think we should
add to our arsenal?
Electricity.
It was how I was able to wake Reign up
and force her back down.
Ooh, I can retrofit something.
- Alex?
- I need to get to Ruby.
I told you, she's in a safe place.
And the less people
that know about that,
the safer the place will be.
I understand that,
but she's probably afraid.
Lena, please let me just
get to her, just in case.
Where Ruby is,
Reign will never find her.
It's not on any maps.
You can't see it from space.
Nobody knows about it,
except for me and my brother.
[BEEPING]
[SUPERGIRL] And how
does Lex know about it?
[LENA] Because it's his mansion.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Patricia Arias,
we need to talk to you.
Let's go.
Mrs. Arias?
Francis Pierce, I told you
that the next time I caught you
in my house looking for pills,
I was gonna put a hole
through your thieving hand.
[GUN COCKS]
Supergirl.
We're sorry if we
startled you, Mrs. Arias.
This is J'onn J'onzz from the FBI.
We have reason to believe that
Reign is on her way here.
Which means this house isn't safe.
We need to get you out of it.
She's her, isn't she?
My Sam is Reign.
How do you know?
I, uh... I never told
her where she was from.
I... [CLICKS TONGUE]
I just wanted her to be normal,
and then when she was ten,
she started doodling
all over her books.
It was like something inside
her just needed to get out...
and I punished her for it.
I grounded her,
and I tore up the pages.
[EXHALES]
So she drew it on the
wall to spite me.
When I saw the same mark
all over the news, I knew.
[SIGHING] Oh, Jesus.
All I ever wanted to
do was to protect her.
That's all I ever wanted.
When we bury things...
And I should've known this, but...
When we bury things,
they come at you even harder.
What Sam's become has nothing to
do with the way she was raised.
I was an awful mother.
I kicked her out.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I've never even met my granddaughter.
Uh...
We need to... [CLEARS THROAT] get
you out of here before she comes.
No, if she's coming here,
I wanna be here when she does.
I kicked her out when I
should've helped her.
I am not gonna turn away from her now.
[MRS. QUELLER EXHALES HEAVILY]
Not much further, Agent Danvers.
I'm fine, Mrs. Queller.
Oh. Of course, you are. [CHUCKLES]
I mean, you're in much
better shape than me.
You don't have these knees
I have to contend with.
Do you know, it took me a week to get
used to the distances in this place.
The step count from
wing to wing, 5,000.
Slightly bigger than my townhouse.
Well, I'm in a studio, so...
And the creepy decor.
Oh, this one.
Worse than the Mona Lisa.
Her eyes follow you everywhere.
Not in a good way.
But, you know, if you can
overlook some of the furnishings
and the fact that the owner
was a serial killer.
Luckily, we haven't found a body yet.
And the amenities are
really quite fantastic.
Ruby doll, look who's
come to pay you a visit.
Aunt Alex.
Hi.
Oh, I'm so glad you're okay.
Is my mom with you?
No. She's still sick.
What's wrong with her?
She won't tell me,
and Lena won't tell me.
Do you know?
No, I don't.
I haven't heard from her in days,
and on the news, there are stories
about the Pestilence outbreak.
Is that what this is?
Was my mom infected?
No, Ruby. No.
I'm 12 years old, Alex.
I can handle anything.
Just tell me what it is.
I would if I knew.
But I don't.
Now, why don't you take me
on a tour of this mausoleum?
I heard there is an indoor pool?
[J'ONN J'ONZZ] Everything is set.
Patricia's in the safe room.
She said we can grab anything
out of the fridge if we want.
She said there's pudding.
- No thanks.
- [BOTH CHUCKLE]
Mon-El and everyone
missed you this morning.
Uh, yeah, I'm sorry about that.
I was, um, dealing with my father.
Since the incident at the DEO, he
has become increasingly depressed.
Irritable, if I push him.
Can Alex prescribe something?
I'm giving him Martian
medicine, which helps.
But the reality is,
with the psychic dampener on,
there isn't really much he can do.
Yeah, I know I needed to protect him,
protect all of us, but...
I still wish there was some way
I could make him feel useful.
There are moments when he doesn't
seem to remember who I am.
Thinks I'm someone from his past.
I'm sorry, J'onn.
It's funny how his past
memories are so clear to him,
yet his present thoughts
are so chaotic.
Hey.
[FAINT RUSTLING]
Pestilence.
How?
Patricia.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Are you home?
[GLASS CRACKS]
Ruby?
Sweetheart, it's Mommy.
I know you're scared.
But I've come back for you.
Did you miss me?
So much.
[SHRIEKING]
[GROANING]
[PATRICIA] Sam!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[PATRICIA] Sam, I
know you're in there.
I know my daughter's in there.
And I need her to understand,
you are not this monster.
You are kind and good. You are
everything that I wasn't.
You're not this.
Honey, if you're listening,
if you can hear me,
I need you to rise up!
Not for me. Not for me, Sam.
This is for Ruby.
For your daughter.
What did you do for your daughter?
- [FLESH SQUELCHES]
- [GROANS]
No!
I love you, Sam.
I forgive you.
[YELLS]
[GRUNTING]
She's dying.
[J'ONN J'ONZZ] Reign's has all
the Worldkiller's powers.
Let's get her out of here.
We gotta go.
[SIGHING]
[BRAINY] Oh, yes.
This view is beautiful.
How long till we reach the disruption?
Five hours, 22 minutes, 16 seconds.
Oh.
That's a shame.
What's a shame?
I was calculating the odds of
Supergirl and DEO defeating Reign
now that her power has tripled.
Tripled?
It appears she's absorbed the
powers of Pestilence and Purity.
Wait, how do you know this?
I bugged the DEO...
In the dirt I gave Winn.
And he thinks he's a
1.42-level intellect.
Why would you bug them?
I grew quite fond of Supergirl
and her compatriots.
I wanted to keep tabs.
Tell me the odds.
On their own, they have a
51% chance of success.
But ironically, if only one
Legionnaire had stayed behind,
their success rate jumps to 88.8%.
Technically, the odds
are in their favor.
Wait, but if Reign absorbed
Pestilence's powers,
then she could still
become the Blight.
Negative. I checked the vitals
of our sleeping Legionnaires.
No Blight.
That's a certainty.
The only certainty.
We have to help them.
Supergirl's fight is not our fight.
Besides, we have to get Imra home.
Supergirl is stronger
than any Legionnaire.
I have faith in her.
So do I.
I'm going to check the stasis chambers
for re-entry into our time.
[PATRICIA GROANS WEAKLY]
[SUPERGIRL] Patricia.
Patricia?
Hey.
Stay with us.
When you see Sam,
you'll tell her that I'm sorry.
That I should have held her close.
And tell Ruby...
Tell her that her grandmother
loved her. [CRYING]
Promise me.
I promise.
[EKG FLATLINING]
[EXHALES]
James.
What is it?
Patricia Arias is dead.
And Reign killed her.
[LENA EXHALES HEAVILY]
And she absorbed Purity
and Pestilence's powers,
so she's now more dangerous than ever.
Lena, you are going to
have to tell Supergirl
that you know how to make Kryptonite.
Oh, no, no. [CHUCKLES]
James, you know I can't do that.
Lena, you have to.
Okay, Reign is out there
killing innocent people,
and you are the only one
with the means to stop her.
You know what happened
when I told Supergirl
I had Kryptonite.
Years of goodwill
vanished in an instant.
- I became the enemy.
- That's not true.
You're not being realistic,
James, okay?
We both know that Supergirl
sees Kryptonite as a personal assault.
She sees it as a hostile
attack on her very nature,
and she will do
everything in her power
to stop me from making it,
even if I'm using it for good.
I just, I can't... I just
can't allow that to happen.
You're right.
Supergirl has seen
Kryptonite in a certain way,
but that's only because your brother
tried to use it to kill Superman.
But this is different.
The world's biggest
enemy happens to have
the same weakness as Supergirl.
So if you come to her as an ally,
with this, to try to
help her catch Reign,
believe me, she will be grateful.
[SIGHS HEAVILY] That's horrible.
Um...
Yeah. No, no, thanks for calling.
[SIGHS]
What's wrong?
Who needs your help, my mom?
Uh, no. No, no one.
Hey, why don't we go watch a movie?
Mrs. Queller told me that
they have Young Frankenstein,
which just so happens to be one
of my all-time favorite movies.
Stop lying to me!
Ruby, I'm not lying, okay?
That call wasn't even about your mom.
She's fine.
So, let's watch a movie.
Right, I'm gonna go
talk to Mrs. Queller,
and she'll hook us up with popcorn
and ice-cold soda, and Gene Wilder.
I mean, come on,
this is gonna be amazing.
You just hang tight.
I'll be right back.
[CAR ALARMS BLARING]
[SIRENS WAILING]
You should be resting.
[EXHALES] I need to be on my feet.
Lying down is just so boring.
[SUPERGIRL SIGHS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
I told Patricia I'd give
a message to Sam, but...
I don't know if I'm ever
gonna see Sam again.
Even with everything I've
learned from Mon-El,
Reign has me outmatched
on every level.
J'onn, how am I gonna fight her?
Usually, your secret weapon
is your heart, Supergirl.
But I didn't see even a glimpse
of humanity left in Reign
that you could reason with.
[SCOFFS]
White Martians are as
soulless as Reign.
When you battled them, were you
ever able to get through to them?
Besides M'gann, no.
But I just used my skills
as a warrior, like you.
But there was one amongst us
who thought they could
reason with them.
And he did.
He got them to spare his life.
Father?
Ursula, you should not have come.
When I told Kemler
I didn't agree with his position
on the Eradicator project,
I wasn't looking to be persuaded.
Father, this is not Ursula.
This is Kara, my friend.
Of course, you are.
We came because we
could use your help.
I'm of no help to any being.
Please leave me be.
- Father, I just need to...
- I said no, J'onn!
Dad, look, I know you cannot journey
through your mind like you once did,
I know that.
But your memories are still intact.
None of it has been lost since
you've been doing the Ta'ar Ka'riq.
You just need help to access it.
I can do nothing for you.
I've had enough failure.
[SUPERGIRL] Um...
J'onn told me that when the
Greens chose to fight the Whites,
you pleaded with those in charge
to have open talks, is that right?
Everyone else just saw
their aggression,
but you saw something
you could reason with.
What was it?
I don't remember.
Father.
Do not play tricks on me.
[J'ONN J'ONZZ] Just look at
me in this form, Father.
Like you did when you saw Ursula.
You remembered exactly
your past conversation.
Now, look at me,
and tell me why you think
you can get through to me.
Get through to you?
[SCOFFS] You're as stubborn
and righteous as Phobos.
I can't persuade you of anything
you don't already believe in.
Whites kept you alive, why?
Because I knew that the sacred scrolls
were important to them.
And inside my mind,
I held all the knowledge and
secrets of those scrolls.
And if they killed you,
that knowledge would be
lost to them forever.
You abandoned your own beliefs
and appealed to theirs.
To their code.
And Reign has been pretty clear
about her code of justice.
Father, you might just
have saved us today.
[CHUCKLES]
I have?
You have.
[J'ONN J'ONZZ AND SUPERGIRL CHUCKLING]
We're approaching the disruption.
Mon-El?
You need to go back.
What?
No. No, despite Brainy's odds,
I'm sure they'll find a
way to defeat Reign.
I'm going with you to the future.
We're near there.
You're saying that because you think
it's what you need to do for me,
out of duty.
But this time needs you, Mon-El.
You need to help them.
And you need to go back
so you can figure out
what's been weighing on your heart.
I'm with you, Imra.
I risked our lives and our
marriage to stop Pestilence.
I still believe it was worth it.
I hoped that once we left,
you'd put your feelings
for Kara behind you.
I swear I never...
You've done nothing wrong.
You've tried to bury your feelings.
You behaved honorably.
You must know that I would never
do anything to dishonor you.
I know.
But I need a man, a partner...
Who will choose me with a full heart.
Go back.
Help her fight Reign.
If you stay, then that's your destiny.
If you return,
I'll know you have no doubts.
- Lena.
- Supergirl.
I have something for you.
But don't be alarmed, it's
in a lead-lined case.
Is that Kryptonite?
- To help you fight Reign.
- [SUPERGIRL SIGHS]
Oh, you have gall, lying to my face.
You know...
I did not lie.
This isn't Lex's, it's mine.
I figured out how to make it,
and I did.
And I supercharged it just for Reign.
You what?
You are going to turn
over the formula to Alex.
You are going to take any
Kryptonian elements from your lab
and bring them to the DEO,
and you are never going to
make Kryptonite ever again.
You know, I knew this
is how you'd react.
But James Olsen convinced me
that we were on the same side.
He thought you'd actually be grateful.
You think I should be grateful
that you learned how to
make the one substance
on this planet that can kill me?
Thousands of things can
kill me, Supergirl.
And everyone else on this planet.
Fire. But we don't go around
banning bonfires or candles.
Cars kill people every day, and
yet we still have the courage
to get in every morning and
drive ourselves to work.
There is one element on the
planet that kills a Kryptonian,
and you can't tolerate its existence.
- No.
- You really do have a god complex.
Do you know what it's
like to walk into a room
and your skin feel like it's going
to be seared off your bones?
Or like nails are running
through your blood?
That's what Kryptonite feels like.
I don't know, it sounds like exactly
what you need to subdue Reign.
I need to be the only person
in control of Kryptonite
on this planet.
Even if I did trust you, even
if we were on the same side,
this substance is so lethal to me
that I can't risk
encountering it by mistake.
Trust is hard for me, too, Supergirl,
but since we seem to need each other,
we're just gonna have
to figure it out.
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
[SAM AND RUBY] Hi, you've reached
he voice-mail of Sam and Ruby.
We can't get to the phone,
so leave us a message.
Mom, please pick up.
I need to see you.
Where are you?
I just wanna talk to you.
Please pick up or come get me.
I need to see you.
Please pick up.
Alright, I think I finally
got the projector working.
You ready?
- You okay?
- Yeah.
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
Ruby.
[GRUNTS]
[ALARM BLARING]
- What is that?
- That's Reign.
Get downstairs now. Go.
It's Reign. She's at Lex's mansion.
[GRUNTS] Which means she
knows Ruby's there.
With Alex.
You can't go.
You're still injured.
But I can use Lena's Kryptonite.
There's no one else.
Actually, there is.
Mon-El.
- The future...
- The future's fine.
Brainy and Imra are still on the way.
Then why did you...
To help you with your
fight against Reign.
[EXHALES]
[ALARM BLARING]
[RUBY WHIMPERS]
[FOOTSTEPS RUNNING]
All right, come on.
I want you to go hide back over there.
And keep your eyes closed.
[MACHINERY WHIRRING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[LOUD CLANG]
[WHIRRING, CLICKING]
[SHRIEKING]
[ALEX PANTING]
[SUPERGIRL] Reign.
Supergirl!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[HIGH-PITCHED TRILLING]
[GROANING]
I can't get a good shot.
[EXHALES]
I got this, Supergirl.
Mom?
- No!
- Ruby, go. Go, go.
Go, get down, down.
[SUPERGIRL] No, you can't.
You would stop me?
I don't have to.
You have a code, a purpose.
You fight against evil and
you dispense justice.
You're here to make a better
world, one without sin in it.
But this girl has not sinned.
You can't kill her.
You won't.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[GUN COCKING, WHIRRING]
[GROANING]
[SIGHS]
- It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
- [CRYING]
[DEVICE BEEPS]
I owe you an apology,
for being so hard on you.
Without your Kryptonite,
we wouldn't have stopped her.
You just have to understand
when it's Kryptonite,
to me that's more than a gun
or any of the other dangers
you were talking about.
It's personal.
It's personal to me, too.
It was a way to help my friend.
I do trust you, Lena.
Good.
[BEEPS]
If you'll both excuse me,
I'm gonna go work on a cure.
Why'd you come back?
Uh... [CHUCKLES]
Well, it seems that Brainy might
have put a nanny cam in Winn's dirt.
That's upsetting.
So Brainy ran some calculations,
and mathematically,
the odds of you beating
Reign in her new form
exponentially increased if one member
of the Legion comes back to help.
As always, I am thankful
for Brainy's calculations.
But you didn't even need me.
Beating Reign using her
ethical code against her?
- It's ingenious.
- I have M'yrnn to thank for that.
And we couldn't have contained
her without you, so...
Hopefully, we can keep her here
until we turn her back to Sam.
Well, I'm not leaving until
the mission's complete.
And I think we should train.
Yeah, okay.
But, uh, later, all right?
I'm gonna go talk to Ruby.
I promised her grandmother I
would tell her something.
Sure.
I have discovered the most
incredible thing today.
Did you know, if you
grind the coffee beans
with the cocoa beans,
you get the most delectable mixture?
It makes the flavor sensors
of my mouth smile.
[CHUCKLES] It's called
a mocha, Father.
"Mocha."
Hmm.
I would've thought, "Choco-coffee."
"Choco-coffee."
You know, that does kind
of have a ring to it.
It's so good to see you
up and around, Father.
You should know that we
were able to catch Reign,
thanks to your advice
about the White Martians.
I have no recollection of
what you're talking about.
Well, all you need to
know is that you helped.
J'onn.
Did you know,
if you grind the coffee
beans with the cocoa beans,
you get the most delectable mixture?
I did not know that, no.
I'd like to try it.
- Thank you.
- [CHUCKLES]
That was her.
I saw her face.
It looks like her, I know. I know.
But I promise you,
that's not your mom.
Why should I believe you?
You promised she was gonna be okay.
You're right.
I didn't tell you the truth.
I was hiding it to try and
protect you, and I...
I see now that that was wrong.
I give you my word
that I will do everything within
my power to keep you safe.
And from here on out,
I will always be honest with you.
Is that okay?
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[EXHALES]
- [LENA] Could you hold the door, please?
- Got it. Ooh.
- Lena.
- Kara.
- You are a sight for sore eyes.
- Hi.
I've been missing you for weeks.
I'm so sorry I haven't been
in touch. It's just...
Oh, don't apologize about anything.
What are you doing here?
- Ah, visiting Ruby.
- Oh.
I didn't know what to bring, so
I brought ice cream. [CHUCKLES]
That's a lot of ice cream.
Did you hear what happened?
Yeah. Yeah, I did.
What an awful day for her.
Yeah, that's an understatement.
[KARA CLICKS TONGUE]
Alex tells me that you're
helping Supergirl fight Reign.
I'm sure she's so
grateful for your help.
Well... Frankly, I am only working
with Supergirl to save Sam
because I have no other choice.
What do you mean?
Well, it's that old adage.
"Never meet your idols,
it'll only lead to disappointment"?
Oh, yes.
Supergirl's not all truth and
justice like she pretends to be.
You know, she had James break into
L-Corp and search my private vault?
I'm sure she had a really good reason.
Of course, James didn't do it.
- Really?
- Well, no.
We've been dating each
other for months.
He knows me, and he trusts
me, and I trust him.
Supergirl went behind my back,
and used my personal
relationships against me.
That's something my mother would do.
She crossed a line.
I can never trust her again.
I didn't know what flavor Ruby
likes, so I bought every flavor.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
I hope you brought your appetite.
Oh, you know me.
[MAN] Tanya, please stop.
[WOMAN] We wanna help you, we promise.
[MAN] In the name of Coville,
please bring us back the journal.
[WOMAN] Tanya!
Subtitle sync and corrections by
awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.